<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Dustin Deus - My personal blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Dustin Deus - My personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Dustin Deus</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Standard formatting in Javascript</title>
      <link>/posts/2017-06-03-js-formatting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2017-06-03-js-formatting/</guid>
      <description>Formatting in Javascript must not be pain. You don&#39;t have to use any linting configurations files. No .eslintrc, .jshintrc, or .jscsrc files to manage. Beside linting it also warns you about programmer errors early e.g unused variables, unhandled errors and more. Give StandardJs a try!
Installation npm install standard --save-dev Editor support  vscode-standardjs vscode-standardjs-snippets  Other editors
Using  Format your code with standard Fix code with standard -fix  Examples Simple integration in your build scripts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An example microservice system using Hemera and best of today</title>
      <link>/posts/aither/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/aither/</guid>
      <description>aither Aither shows an approach how to bootstrap a microservice system with Hemera and docker. You can scale your worker in seconds and because we use NATS as “nervous system&amp;rdquo; for our distributed system we do not have to carry about service-discovery or load-balancing of hemera-services. We use traefik to load-balancing the api-gateway.
This configuration will setup:
 Hapi http server which act as api-gataway to the Hemera services. Microservice example which is responsible to add two numbers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hemera - A Node.js microservices toolkit for NATS</title>
      <link>/posts/hemera/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hemera/</guid>
      <description>Hemera (/ˈhɛmərə/; Ancient Greek: Ἡμέρα [hɛːméra] &amp;ldquo;day&amp;rdquo;) is a small wrapper around the NATS driver. NATS is a simple, fast and reliable solution for the internal communication of a distributed system. It chooses simplicity and reliability over guaranteed delivery. We want to provide a toolkit to develop micro services in an easy and powerful way. We provide a pattern matching RPC style. You don&#39;t have to worry about the transport. NATS is powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The classic developer nowadays ...</title>
      <link>/posts/the-classic-developer-nowadays/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/the-classic-developer-nowadays/</guid>
      <description>You use Javascript with a powerful framework like Angular or React to implement a great user experience. Perhaps you want to get the most of the line and use babel. You love automatism and create your own build pipeline with gulp or grunt. You are hungry for a REST API to play with data in your application. Your API is build with proven software like NodeJs, .NET Core or Spring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! My name is Dustin and I’m fullstack software engineer from Germany. I have an extensive experience in software development in consideration of high quality standards.
To me, fullstack really means:
 Choose the correct repo strategy (single or mono). Setup a CI/DI pipeline. Deploy with zero downtime. Scale and rollback at any time. Infrastructure changes and builds are reproducible. Programming language and application frameworks are choosen based on team-knowledge and project requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>